<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LooseCanon xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <Scraped>2014-03-01T13:04:39.7840467+11:00</Scraped>
  <Url>\\linuxb0x\store\www.loose-canon.info</Url>
  <Books>
    <Book Number="0">
      <FileName>page2.htm</FileName>
      <Name>Empty</Name>
      <Chapters />
      <Abbreviation>00</Abbreviation>
    </Book>
    <Book Number="1">
      <FileName>page4.htm</FileName>
      <Name>Empty</Name>
      <Chapters />
      <Abbreviation>01</Abbreviation>
    </Book>
    <Book Number="2">
      <FileName>page5.htm</FileName>
      <Name>Empty</Name>
      <Chapters />
      <Abbreviation>02</Abbreviation>
    </Book>
    <Book Number="3">
      <FileName>page6.htm</FileName>
      <Name>Empty</Name>
      <Chapters />
      <Abbreviation>03</Abbreviation>
    </Book>
    <Book Number="4">
      <FileName>page7.htm</FileName>
      <Name>Empty</Name>
      <Chapters />
      <Abbreviation>04</Abbreviation>
    </Book>
    <Book Number="5">
      <FileName>page8.htm</FileName>
      <Name>Empty</Name>
      <Chapters />
      <Abbreviation>05</Abbreviation>
    </Book>
    <Book Number="6">
      <FileName>page9.htm</FileName>
      <Name>Empty</Name>
      <Chapters />
      <Abbreviation>06</Abbreviation>
    </Book>
    <Book Number="7">
      <FileName>page10.htm</FileName>
      <Name>Empty</Name>
      <Chapters />
      <Abbreviation>07</Abbreviation>
    </Book>
    <Book Number="8">
      <FileName>page11.htm</FileName>
      <Name>Empty</Name>
      <Chapters />
      <Abbreviation>08</Abbreviation>
    </Book>
    <Book Number="9">
      <FileName>page12.htm</FileName>
      <Name>Empty</Name>
      <Chapters />
      <Abbreviation>09</Abbreviation>
    </Book>
    <Book Number="10">
      <FileName>page13.htm</FileName>
      <Name>Empty</Name>
      <Chapters />
      <Abbreviation>10</Abbreviation>
    </Book>
    <Book Number="11">
      <FileName>page14.htm</FileName>
      <Name>Empty</Name>
      <Chapters />
      <Abbreviation>11</Abbreviation>
    </Book>
    <Book Number="12">
      <FileName>page15.htm</FileName>
      <Name>Empty</Name>
      <Chapters />
      <Abbreviation>12</Abbreviation>
    </Book>
    <Book Number="13">
      <FileName>page16.htm</FileName>
      <Name>Empty</Name>
      <Chapters />
      <Abbreviation>13</Abbreviation>
    </Book>
    <Book Number="14">
      <FileName>page17.htm</FileName>
      <Name>Empty</Name>
      <Chapters />
      <Abbreviation>14</Abbreviation>
    </Book>
    <Book Number="15">
      <FileName>page18.htm</FileName>
      <Name>Empty</Name>
      <Chapters />
      <Abbreviation>15</Abbreviation>
    </Book>
    <Book Number="16">
      <FileName>page19.htm</FileName>
      <Name>Empty</Name>
      <Chapters />
      <Abbreviation>16</Abbreviation>
    </Book>
    <Book Number="17">
      <FileName>page20.htm</FileName>
      <Name>Empty</Name>
      <Chapters />
      <Abbreviation>17</Abbreviation>
    </Book>
    <Book Number="18">
      <FileName>page21.htm</FileName>
      <Name>Frequently Asked Questions</Name>
      <Chapters>
        <Chapter Number="1">
          <Verses>
            <Verse Number="1">
              <Text>Ages ago, there was a young, inquisitive pirate who was called Frequently. He had a tendency to ask a lot of questions</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="2">
              <Text>One day, his mates told him of the glory that was the Flying Spaghetti Monster.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="3">
              <Text>Wanting to know more, Frequently sought out the wise and learned Dalai Llama, who was in fact an alpaca, and Frequently Asked Questions.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="4">
              <Text>Frequently Asked: “Hey, wouldn’t it be funny to say that the Flying Spaghetti Monster has spoken to me, come to me in a dream, I am the Flying Spaghetti Monster, and demand that you follow my ignorant, unsubstantiated schism or else be wrong?”</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="5">
              <Text>And the Dalai Llama Answered: “No.”</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="6">
              <Text>Frequently Asked: “Hey, I see that you disagree with the teaching of intelligent design in school.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="7">
              <Text>Does this mean I can assume that you also abhor Christianity?</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="8">
              <Text>Does this mean that we share every single remotely religious or moral belief?</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="9">
              <Text>Does this mean that I can be an intolerant jackass, because everybody has to agree with me?”</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="10">
              <Text>And the Dalai Llama Answered: “No.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="11">
              <Text>Pastafarianism is intended to protest attempts to include religion in science curriculum.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="12">
              <Text>We are in no way against religion itself, and we do not appreciate being portrayed as such by radical people who consider this the perfect vehicle to spread their inane doctrines.”</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="13">
              <Text>Frequently Asked: Are you ever not going to answer “no?”</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="14">
              <Text>And the Dalai Llama Answered: “Maybe.”</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="15">
              <Text>Frequently Asked: “What’s the Pastafarian position on some political issue not related to intelligent design?”</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="16">
              <Text>And the Dalai Llama Answered: “I have absolutely no idea.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="17">
              <Text>But we can discuss it intelligently.”</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="18">
              <Text>Frequently Asked: “Are you people for real?”</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="19">
              <Text>And the Dalai Llama Answered: “Yes. We’re real people.”</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="20">
              <Text>Frequently Asked: “Seriously.”</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="21">
              <Text>And the Dalai Llama Answered: “Yes.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="22">
              <Text>We all fervently believe that the universe was created by a Flying Spaghetti Monster, who designed it to appear older than it really was, and make it look like it worked in ways similar to logical conjectures made on overwhelming observable evidence, but actually wasn’t, and actually didn’t, because He ultimately controls it all with His Noodly Appendage!”</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="23">
              <Text>Frequently Asked: “Really?”</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="24">
              <Text>And the Dalai Llama produced audible ellipses.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="25">
              <Text>Frequently Asked: “Okay, I get it.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="26">
              <Text>So why a Spaghetti Monster?”</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="27">
              <Text>And the Dalai Llama Answered: “Why not?</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="28">
              <Text>Has better ring to it than “bearded white guy.”</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="29">
              <Text>Besides, ask Bobby.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="30">
              <Text>It was his revelation.”</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="31">
              <Text>Frequently Asked: “You guys know you’re going to Hell, right?”</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="32">
              <Text>And the Dalai Llama Answered: “That’s your opinion.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="33">
              <Text>We try to be tolerant of your opinions, so could you at least try to tolerate ours?”</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="34">
              <Text>Frequently Asked: “Speaking of Hell, what’s that like?</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="35">
              <Text>I know that Heaven has a stripper factory and a beer volcano, but is there anything else?”</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="36">
              <Text>And the Dalai Llama Answered: “If you’re a true believer in whatever faith you’re a part of, and you’ve done what’s expected of you, then that’s the Afterlife you get.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="37">
              <Text>The Flying Spaghetti Monster has no territorial disputes with anybody else.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="38">
              <Text>If you’re not going there, we’ll take you, and it may not be fun, but it beats the hell (haha! hell!) outta Lakes of Fire.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="39">
              <Text>“There will be a kind of HellLight, where unbelievers have to live with school cafeteria spaghetti, second rate beer, and boring jobs in the service industries where the Heavenbound Pastafarians will be living.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="40">
              <Text>There will be no privation, no physical torture, no burning or boiling in various liquids.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="41">
              <Text>These aren’t bad people, these are people that followed the culture and customs of their times and did not recognize the difference between a culture and a faith.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="42">
              <Text>And this HellLight will include a just and equitable redemption process.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="43">
              <Text>“Actual Pastafarian Hell is reserved for a very few, and those will be divided from the Pasta, the finest beverages and the fellowship of persons of good will and kind intent.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="44">
              <Text>They will do all the laundry, cleaning and heavy or unpleasant jobs that are there.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="45">
              <Text>Never will they eat of the Pasta of any kind, but will live on lots of beans and rice, potatoes and extremely cheap cuts of meat, and the type of diet that the American urban poor can afford, or that Senior Citizens and disabled persons on Social Security are reduced to.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="46">
              <Text>They get the really icky dirty work.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="47">
              <Text>They deserve it.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="48">
              <Text>The bullies of the geopolitical world will be there, and their helpers.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="49">
              <Text>The false religious leaders, who plead for funds through electronic media, and give nothing of their true selves, and hoard the money and live in opulence, they will be there.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="50">
              <Text>Many others of ill-intent will be with them.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="51">
              <Text>“There is a reservation there for the tricksters, the con-men, the corrupt, unrepentant politicians, who will begin every work day by licking clean the footwear of every Native American person there, even in HellLight.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="52">
              <Text>Also there will be the promulgators of the horrible practices against the indigenous people of every country ever “modernized” by Western Civilization.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="53">
              <Text>They lick boots as well.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="54">
              <Text>And when they’re through they get to do all the stuff that nobody in the Hell above them want to do.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="55">
              <Text>“Not a real burning-in type hell, no boiling lakes of fire, just an appropriate “reward.”</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="56">
              <Text>No more lunatics and sadists, please.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="57">
              <Text>“Other people have other ideas, but then again other people are promoting Holy War, too.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="58">
              <Text>Don’t do that in the name of our FSM.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="59">
              <Text>That’s not the Way to Do Things Right.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="60">
              <Text>Then again, we could be completely wrong.”</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="61">
              <Text>Frequently Asked: “Oooh, What about the Pastafarian equivalent of such-and-such element of such-and-such religion that you didn’t cover above?”</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="62">
              <Text>And the Dalai Llama Answered: “We’re not trying to completely copy and twist everything about religion.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="63">
              <Text>We don’t take issue with religion; we take issue with it being taught as science.”</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="64">
              <Text>Frequently Asked: “Well, one aspect of other religions you do have is a god.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="65">
              <Text>Who happens to be made of pasta.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="66">
              <Text>Isn’t it sorta wrong to eat what He’s made of?”</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="67">
              <Text>And the Dalai Llama Answered: “Eat some of this bread instead, and wash it down with this wine, then.”</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="68">
              <Text>Frequently Asked: “What?”</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="69">
              <Text>And the Dalai Llama Answered: “The Flying Spaghetti Monster is not pasta, but a deity who chooses to represent Himself as pasta.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="70">
              <Text>If you like Pasta, go ahead and eat some.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="71">
              <Text>He doesn’t mind, because the Sharing of the Pasta is a form of worship.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="72">
              <Text>Especially the sharing part.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="73">
              <Text>Transubstantiation is not part of Pastafarian doctrine.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="74">
              <Text>That means when you eat Pasta, you aren’t eating Him, but eating Pasta.”</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="75">
              <Text>Frequently Asked: “So, I’d love to eat pasta, but I have some sort of medical condition/diet/personal preference that prevents me from doing so.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="76">
              <Text>What do I do?”</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="77">
              <Text>And the Dalai Llama Answered: “His Noodly Majesty is, above all, tolerant.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="78">
              <Text>Be a good person, and you’ll be fine, eating Pasta or not.”</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="79">
              <Text>Frequently Asked: “What if I don’t have a set of pirate regalia?</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="80">
              <Text>What if I don’t drink beer?</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="81">
              <Text>What if I think strippers are immoral?”</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="82">
              <Text>And the Dalai Llama Answered: “Tolerance.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="83">
              <Text>You’ll be okay.”</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="84">
              <Text>Frequently Asked: “Speaking of pirates, did you know about Talk Like a Pirate day?”</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="85">
              <Text>And the Dalai Llama Answered: “Yes.”</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="86">
              <Text>Frequently Asked: “Speaking of beer, what kind of beer is in the volcano?</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="87">
              <Text>What if it’s not my favorite?</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="88">
              <Text>What are the strippers like?</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="89">
              <Text>What if I’m a woman and want a man?</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="90">
              <Text>What if I’m looking for a relationship, not just short-term fun?</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="91">
              <Text>What if…”</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="92">
              <Text>And the Dalai Llama Answered: “He is omniscient and omnipotent.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="93">
              <Text>You’ll be well taken care of in Heaven, in a way that will suit your wants and needs exactly.”</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="94">
              <Text>Frequently Asked: “Cool, I get it!</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="95">
              <Text>By the way, what’s the best way to be sarcastic and condescending to those who I think are idiots?</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="96">
              <Text>What about all those people who don’t subscribe to whatever specific religious or other philosophy I might have?</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="97">
              <Text>They really need to learn that the universe revolves around me.”</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="98">
              <Text>And the Dalai Llama Answered: “No, you don’t get it.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="99">
              <Text>Tolerance.”</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="100">
              <Text>Frequently Asked: “Okay, so I do get it.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="101">
              <Text>How long has this been around, anyway?”</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="102">
              <Text>And the Dalai Llama Answered: “His Noodly Majesty has been around since the beginning of the universe, which he created.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="103">
              <Text>If you’re asking when He revealed Himself to Bobby Henderson, you’re asking about May 2005 CE.”</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="104">
              <Text>Frequently Asked: “And how many Pastafarians are there?”</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="105">
              <Text>And the Dalai Llama Answered: “Millions, scattered around the planet.”</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="106">
              <Text>Frequently Asked: “Really?</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="107">
              <Text>Wow!”</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="108">
              <Text>And the Dalai Llama Answered: “Actually, we have no clue.”</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="109">
              <Text>Frequently Asked: “Oh, either way, add 1 to that number, because I’m in!</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="110">
              <Text>Now, what can I do to help?”</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="111">
              <Text>And the Dalai Llama Answered: “Spread His Word among your peers!</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="112">
              <Text>Or, if you’re feeling philanthropic, help needy people.”</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="113">
              <Text>And Frequently left the presence of the Dalai Llama who was in fact an alpaca, and lived the rest of his life a wonderful and loving Pastafarian, if not persistently inquisitive.</Text>
            </Verse>
          </Verses>
        </Chapter>
      </Chapters>
      <Abbreviation>faq</Abbreviation>
    </Book>
    <Book Number="19">
      <FileName>page22.htm</FileName>
      <Name>Empty</Name>
      <Chapters />
      <Abbreviation>19</Abbreviation>
    </Book>
    <Book Number="20">
      <FileName>page23.htm</FileName>
      <Name>Empty</Name>
      <Chapters />
      <Abbreviation>20</Abbreviation>
    </Book>
    <Book Number="21">
      <FileName>page24.htm</FileName>
      <Name>Empty</Name>
      <Chapters />
      <Abbreviation>21</Abbreviation>
    </Book>
    <Book Number="22">
      <FileName>page25.htm</FileName>
      <Name>Empty</Name>
      <Chapters />
      <Abbreviation>22</Abbreviation>
    </Book>
    <Book Number="23">
      <FileName>page26.htm</FileName>
      <Name>Empty</Name>
      <Chapters />
      <Abbreviation>23</Abbreviation>
    </Book>
    <Book Number="24">
      <FileName>page27.htm</FileName>
      <Name>Empty</Name>
      <Chapters />
      <Abbreviation>24</Abbreviation>
    </Book>
    <Book Number="25">
      <FileName>page28.htm</FileName>
      <Name>Empty</Name>
      <Chapters />
      <Abbreviation>25</Abbreviation>
    </Book>
    <Book Number="26">
      <FileName>page29.htm</FileName>
      <Name>Empty</Name>
      <Chapters />
      <Abbreviation>26</Abbreviation>
    </Book>
    <Book Number="27">
      <FileName>page30.htm</FileName>
      <Name>Empty</Name>
      <Chapters />
      <Abbreviation>27</Abbreviation>
    </Book>
    <Book Number="28">
      <FileName>page31.htm</FileName>
      <Name>Empty</Name>
      <Chapters />
      <Abbreviation>28</Abbreviation>
    </Book>
    <Book Number="29">
      <FileName>page32.htm</FileName>
      <Name>Empty</Name>
      <Chapters />
      <Abbreviation>29</Abbreviation>
    </Book>
    <Book Number="30">
      <FileName>page33.htm</FileName>
      <Name>Empty</Name>
      <Chapters />
      <Abbreviation>30</Abbreviation>
    </Book>
    <Book Number="31">
      <FileName>page34.htm</FileName>
      <Name>Empty</Name>
      <Chapters />
      <Abbreviation>31</Abbreviation>
    </Book>
    <Book Number="32">
      <FileName>page35.htm</FileName>
      <Name>Empty</Name>
      <Chapters />
      <Abbreviation>32</Abbreviation>
    </Book>
    <Book Number="33">
      <FileName>page36.htm</FileName>
      <Name>Empty</Name>
      <Chapters />
      <Abbreviation>33</Abbreviation>
    </Book>
    <Book Number="34">
      <FileName>page37.htm</FileName>
      <Name>Empty</Name>
      <Chapters />
      <Abbreviation>34</Abbreviation>
    </Book>
    <Book Number="35">
      <FileName>page38.htm</FileName>
      <Name>Empty</Name>
      <Chapters />
      <Abbreviation>35</Abbreviation>
    </Book>
    <Book Number="36">
      <FileName>page39.htm</FileName>
      <Name>Empty</Name>
      <Chapters />
      <Abbreviation>36</Abbreviation>
    </Book>
    <Book Number="37">
      <FileName>page40.htm</FileName>
      <Name>Empty</Name>
      <Chapters />
      <Abbreviation>37</Abbreviation>
    </Book>
    <Book Number="38">
      <FileName>page41.htm</FileName>
      <Name>Empty</Name>
      <Chapters />
      <Abbreviation>38</Abbreviation>
    </Book>
    <Book Number="39">
      <FileName>page42.htm</FileName>
      <Name>Empty</Name>
      <Chapters />
      <Abbreviation>39</Abbreviation>
    </Book>
    <Book Number="40">
      <FileName>page43.htm</FileName>
      <Name>Empty</Name>
      <Chapters />
      <Abbreviation>40</Abbreviation>
    </Book>
    <Book Number="41">
      <FileName>page44.htm</FileName>
      <Name>Empty</Name>
      <Chapters />
      <Abbreviation>41</Abbreviation>
    </Book>
    <Book Number="42">
      <FileName>page45.htm</FileName>
      <Name>Empty</Name>
      <Chapters />
      <Abbreviation>42</Abbreviation>
    </Book>
    <Book Number="43">
      <FileName>page46.htm</FileName>
      <Name>Empty</Name>
      <Chapters />
      <Abbreviation>43</Abbreviation>
    </Book>
    <Book Number="44">
      <FileName>page47.htm</FileName>
      <Name>Empty</Name>
      <Chapters />
      <Abbreviation>44</Abbreviation>
    </Book>
    <Book Number="45">
      <FileName>page48.htm</FileName>
      <Name>Empty</Name>
      <Chapters />
      <Abbreviation>45</Abbreviation>
    </Book>
    <Book Number="46">
      <FileName>page49.htm</FileName>
      <Name>Empty</Name>
      <Chapters />
      <Abbreviation>46</Abbreviation>
    </Book>
    <Book Number="47">
      <FileName>page50.htm</FileName>
      <Name>Empty</Name>
      <Chapters />
      <Abbreviation>47</Abbreviation>
    </Book>
    <Book Number="48">
      <FileName>page51.htm</FileName>
      <Name>Empty</Name>
      <Chapters />
      <Abbreviation>48</Abbreviation>
    </Book>
    <Book Number="49">
      <FileName>page52.htm</FileName>
      <Name>Empty</Name>
      <Chapters />
      <Abbreviation>49</Abbreviation>
    </Book>
    <Book Number="50">
      <FileName>page53.htm</FileName>
      <Name>Empty</Name>
      <Chapters />
      <Abbreviation>50</Abbreviation>
    </Book>
    <Book Number="51">
      <FileName>page54.htm</FileName>
      <Name>Empty</Name>
      <Chapters />
      <Abbreviation>51</Abbreviation>
    </Book>
    <Book Number="52">
      <FileName>page55.htm</FileName>
      <Name>Empty</Name>
      <Chapters />
      <Abbreviation>52</Abbreviation>
    </Book>
  </Books>
</LooseCanon>