<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LooseCanon xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <Scraped>2014-03-01T12:52:33.6975169+11:00</Scraped>
  <Url>\\linuxb0x\store\www.loose-canon.info</Url>
  <Books>
    <Book Number="0">
      <FileName>page2.htm</FileName>
      <Name>Empty</Name>
      <Chapters />
      <Abbreviation>00</Abbreviation>
    </Book>
    <Book Number="1">
      <FileName>page4.htm</FileName>
      <Name>Empty</Name>
      <Chapters />
      <Abbreviation>01</Abbreviation>
    </Book>
    <Book Number="2">
      <FileName>page5.htm</FileName>
      <Name>Empty</Name>
      <Chapters />
      <Abbreviation>02</Abbreviation>
    </Book>
    <Book Number="3">
      <FileName>page6.htm</FileName>
      <Name>Empty</Name>
      <Chapters />
      <Abbreviation>03</Abbreviation>
    </Book>
    <Book Number="4">
      <FileName>page7.htm</FileName>
      <Name>Empty</Name>
      <Chapters />
      <Abbreviation>04</Abbreviation>
    </Book>
    <Book Number="5">
      <FileName>page8.htm</FileName>
      <Name>Empty</Name>
      <Chapters />
      <Abbreviation>05</Abbreviation>
    </Book>
    <Book Number="6">
      <FileName>page9.htm</FileName>
      <Name>Empty</Name>
      <Chapters />
      <Abbreviation>06</Abbreviation>
    </Book>
    <Book Number="7">
      <FileName>page10.htm</FileName>
      <Name>Empty</Name>
      <Chapters />
      <Abbreviation>07</Abbreviation>
    </Book>
    <Book Number="8">
      <FileName>page11.htm</FileName>
      <Name>Empty</Name>
      <Chapters />
      <Abbreviation>08</Abbreviation>
    </Book>
    <Book Number="9">
      <FileName>page12.htm</FileName>
      <Name>Empty</Name>
      <Chapters />
      <Abbreviation>09</Abbreviation>
    </Book>
    <Book Number="10">
      <FileName>page13.htm</FileName>
      <Name>The Book of Fearsome Pirate Pete</Name>
      <Chapters>
        <Chapter Number="1">
          <Verses>
            <Verse Number="1">
              <Text>Long ago, in an allegorical Caribbean filled with anachronisms and wisdom, there was a pirate known only as Fearsome Pirate Pete.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="2">
              <Text>He was determined to become the greatest pirate the Caribbean had ever known.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="3">
              <Text>Having discovered that simply being Piratical all the time with great enthusiasm was not quite enough, Pete explored different schools of piratical thought.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="4">
              <Text>One day, he sat down to think for a very long while.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="5">
              <Text>While he was sitting, fully decked out in Pirate regalia, he was a very easy target for any nearby Ninjas, or so it seemed.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="6">
              <Text>A Ninja did notice Pete, and did try to sneak upon him and stab him through his back.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="7">
              <Text>However, the Ninjas blade became caught in Pete’s back hair, never reaching Pete himself.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="8">
              <Text>Pete turned around, and slugged the Ninja square in the face.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="9">
              <Text>Now, some other Pirates were nearby at saw the event.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="10">
              <Text>They immediately recognized Pete’s Fearsomeness, and swore allegiance on the spot, becoming his new crew.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="11">
              <Text>Now, Fearsome Pirate Pete’s favorite followers were Nikta, and Tiny the midget.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="12">
              <Text>Nikta suggested that Pete try Atkinsceticism, to eat very little, and if eating anything at all, for it to be very low in carbohydrates.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="13">
              <Text>Fearsome Pirate Pete and his crew tried this for one day, but by the second day, Pete began to have strange pains in his stomach.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="14">
              <Text>Soon, Pete was light-headed, and began to hallucinate.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="15">
              <Text>Seemingly in front of his eyes, Pete saw a blurry mass of yellow centered around two large red circles.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="16">
              <Text>The strange figure said unto Pete, “Everything in moderation, even moderation.” 2.7 But Pete was snapped out of his daze by Nikta.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="17">
              <Text>“Perhaps you ate too much, Pete?” Nikta asked.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="18">
              <Text>“Nar,” Pete responded, “Perhaps Oi been eatin’ too little!”</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="19">
              <Text>“I’ve heard of good Italian food high in carbohydrates, and apparently very good for the soul.” Tiny said.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="20">
              <Text>“What? That’s the exact opposite of what I’m trying to get you guys to do!” Nikta said aloud.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="21">
              <Text>“Yarr, but methinks it be’n time fer a change,” Pete said, “Oi be havin’ a good feelin’ about this’r Pasta stuff.”</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="22">
              <Text>And with that, Nikta stormed off in a rage.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="23">
              <Text>Now, Fearsome Pirate Pete and Tiny bought some Spaghetti and Meatballs from a local Italian restaurant, and sat down to eat it.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="24">
              <Text>Fearsome Pirate Pete did eat much of the Spaghetti and Meatballs, and as he ate, the Spaghetti did replenish itself.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="25">
              <Text>The more Pete ate, the more Spaghetti there was for him to eat.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="26">
              <Text>Yea, Tiny did observe this miracle, and was awestruck.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="27">
              <Text>It was then that Nikta returned with many Ninjas, and they all came down upon Pete in a horrible fury.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="28">
              <Text>But Pete did not budge, he sat contently eating his Spaghetti as the Ninjas came to kill him.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="29">
              <Text>The Ninjas could not touch Pete, though.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="30">
              <Text>For when the Ninjas came too close, the Spaghetti came alive with divine energy, and struck at the Ninjas.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="31">
              <Text>Furious, Nikta attacked Pete himself, but was caught in the animated Spaghetti, and thrown out the window.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="32">
              <Text>The Spaghetti began to rise, floating in air.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="33">
              <Text>The Spaghetti took with it two meatballs, and grew googly eyestalks.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="34">
              <Text>Fearsome Pirate Pete was in awe of the Pasta, and he did speak to it.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="35">
              <Text>“Whart be ye? Some fashion o’ Monster o’ Spaghetti what Flies?” Fearsome Pirate Pete did ask.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="36">
              <Text>The Pasta responded, “Yes, Pete, though you really should just call me the Flying Spaghetti Monster.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="37">
              <Text>A name is like a fine beverage, it should please the tongue to interact with it.”</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="38">
              <Text>“Aye… y’mean it rolls off the tongue?” Fearsome Pirate Pete did ask.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="39">
              <Text>With a sigh, the Flying Spaghetti Monster replied, “Yes, that’s exactly what I mean.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="40">
              <Text>Now, I have chosen you to be a greatly exaggerated and fictitious character for the purposes of teaching my ways to my followers.”</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="41">
              <Text>“Yarrgh, that be soundin’ loike a good plan” Fearsome Pirate Pete agreed.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="42">
              <Text>“’Course it is,” The Flying Spaghetti Monster responded, “First, you must be taught a little of the history of the world.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="43">
              <Text>Narrator, if you would.”</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="44">
              <Text>In The Beginning, or so the Flying Spaghetti Monster calls the first time He can remember waking up from a hangover, He was flying above the meeting of a great ocean and land.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="45">
              <Text>The land was inhabited by nothing more than Mountains, Trees, and a Midget.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="46">
              <Text>The Midget cried up to the Flying Spaghetti Monster in great anguish.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="47">
              <Text>“I’m bored!” The midget wailed.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="48">
              <Text>“O Flying Spaghetti Monster, creator of all things as far as I can tell, perform some miracle, cure me of my boredom!” The midget prayed.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="49">
              <Text>Now, the Flying Spaghetti Monster was not in the habit of taking requests, but having little else to do and being bored himself, the Great Noodly One touched the ocean with His Noodly Appendage, and forth from that point spawned the whole of the earth.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="50">
              <Text>With a second touch of His Noodly Appendage, the Flying Spaghetti Monster bestowed upon the Midget the finest of Pirate Regalia.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="51">
              <Text>The Flying Spaghetti Monster then commanded him, “Go forth, pillage, plunder, eat, drink, and have a fun time running from boredom.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="52">
              <Text>In other words, be a Pirate!”</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="53">
              <Text>The midget was ecstatic, but had one question.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="54">
              <Text>“That’s it?</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="55">
              <Text>No commandments, suggestions, guidelines, bylaws you want me to live by?” the Midget asked his Delicious Lord.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="56">
              <Text>“Ah, you’ll hear about those later,” The Flying Spaghetti Monster explained, “Right now I want to get back to Fearsome Pirate Pete.”</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="57">
              <Text>The Midget still did not understand the ways of the Flying Spaghetti Monster, but he knew he was not truly meant to.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="58">
              <Text>“There is another thing you should know, and this will help you to recruit more followers,” The Flying Spaghetti Monster told Pete.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="59">
              <Text>“When you die, your soul, which I think is immortal, but don’t quote me on that, will find it’s way to Pastafarian Heaven, where there is a Volcano of Beer, and a Factory of Strippers.”</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="60">
              <Text>“But O Noodly Lord, Oi be prefer’n Grog t’ Beer… Will Oi have to drink only Beer in heaven?” Fearsome Pirate Pete asked the Flying Spaghetti Monster.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="61">
              <Text>“What?</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="62">
              <Text>Of course not!</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="63">
              <Text>Oh, I forgot again, the Beer Volcano is really a Volcano of any beverage you like, whenever you like it.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="64">
              <Text>I prefer Beer, so that’s all it is to me, I forget sometimes,” The Flying Spaghetti Monster explained, “Similar rules apply to the Stripper Factory.”</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="65">
              <Text>“Yarrgh, one other thing,” Fearsome Pirate Pete continued, “Ye said summin ‘bout Pastafarian?</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="66">
              <Text>What be that?”</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="67">
              <Text>“Did I forget that too?” The Great Noodly One asked rhetorically, “Sheesh.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="68">
              <Text>Pastafarian is what you will call yourself, and what any follower of Me will call themselves.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="69">
              <Text>I’m going to say that covers everything,” The Flying Spaghetti Monster concluded, “Because I just remembered that I left Lasagna in the oven.”</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="70">
              <Text>In one moment the Flying Spaghetti Monster was there, and in the next, He was not.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="71">
              <Text>Fearsome Pirate Pete then began the work of assembling his crew.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="72">
              <Text>Tiny became Pete’s first mate.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="73">
              <Text>Going to various bars and taverns, Pete was able to assemble a motley crew of salty seadogs who all enjoyed Pasta.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="74">
              <Text>In one bar in particular, he saw a strangely dressed Pirate, with pale skin and a horned helm, brawling with many Pirates, wielding a large hammer.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="75">
              <Text>“Yarrgh, what be yer name?” Pete asked him once he had incapacitated all the Pirates in the bar.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="76">
              <Text>“My name is Ushnor, the Great and Awesome,” he replied.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="77">
              <Text>“Oh, ye think yer high ‘n mighty, do ye?” Pete asked him.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="78">
              <Text>“I got the title because of my hammer, everybody started calling me Ushnor the Great and Awesome after I smashed some fool’s head open in a bar one night,” Ushnor explained.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="79">
              <Text>“Yar. Me likes yer style. Ye be me new second mate, if’n ye like,” Pete offered.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="80">
              <Text>The next day, Fearsome Pirate Pete called together his first and second mate, Tiny and Ushnor, to decide where to set sail for.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="81">
              <Text>“I have a request, Captain,” Ushnor asked, “There is a holiday in my homeland in the North soon.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="82">
              <Text>It’s dedicated to Thor, and we chase down wild hogs, and bash their skulls open with our hammers.”</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="83">
              <Text>“But what about pillaging, and being a Pirate?” Tiny asked.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="84">
              <Text>“Now Tiny,” Pete said, “Oi’m sure this be a very important holiday fer Ushnor.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="85">
              <Text>We must be understandin’ and tolerant of others beliefs and practices, and sometimes we just need t’ go with the flow.”</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="86">
              <Text>And Lo, they did set out for the North.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="87">
              <Text>For three and twenty days and three and twenty nights did they sail, until the sea became slushy with ice, and the wind chilled the very bones of even the largest Pirates.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="88">
              <Text>Suddenly, their ship was struck by some great tentacly thing, and the ship began to sink.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="89">
              <Text>Fearsome Pirate Pete jumped into the ocean, and swam until he found land.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="90">
              <Text>Upon reaching land, Pete did pass out from exhaustion.</Text>
            </Verse>
          </Verses>
        </Chapter>
        <Chapter Number="2">
          <Verses>
            <Verse Number="1">
              <Text>Fearsome Pirate Pete was woken up rather rudely by a Penguin.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="2">
              <Text>The penguin pecked at his eyes until Pete rose and whacked it across the head.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="3">
              <Text>“Bloody hell Tiny, enough’s enou-” Pete said waking up.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="4">
              <Text>Upon seeing the desolate landscape, and a rather confused Penguin, Pete was thoroughly confused.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="5">
              <Text>“I say, why did you just slap me across the face, chap?” The Penguin inquired.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="6">
              <Text>“What in the name of Penne… yer a talking penguin!” Pete exclaimed as he stood up.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="7">
              <Text>“And you are a gorilla who smells like alcohol,” The Penguin retorted.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="8">
              <Text>“Arrgh, let’s not be callin’ names here. Where the bloody hell are we anyway?” Pete asked.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="9">
              <Text>“Well I was going to ask you ol’ chap, but you seem rather hostile,” The Penguin explained.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="10">
              <Text>“Me greatest apologies, it’s not like Oi be wakin’ up getting poked in the eye every day,” Pete apologized.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="11">
              <Text>“Quite.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="12">
              <Text>My name is Bob,” Bob reached out a flipper.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="13">
              <Text>Pete said, still somewhat dazed, “Me name’s Fearsome Pirate Pete.”</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="14">
              <Text>“Charming.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="15">
              <Text>Lets get moving shall we?” Bob proposed.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="16">
              <Text>“Where the ruddy hell be we goin’?” Pete asked.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="17">
              <Text>“Well, where are you going?” Bob said blankly.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="18">
              <Text>“Well, there be this Norse festival involvin’ smashing the sku… uh… big feast, lots of food.” Pete caught himself before possibly offending Bob.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="19">
              <Text>“Right, well then, we mustn’t be late,” said Bob as he started waddling off in a direction, as if he knew exactly where he was going.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="20">
              <Text>“Where the bloody hell am I…” muttered Pete.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="21">
              <Text>Fearsome Pirate Pete and Bob traveled far through the wintry wasteland.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="22">
              <Text>“D’ye know of any dangers in these lands?” Pete asked once.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="23">
              <Text>Bobs sole response was, “Not a clue.”</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="24">
              <Text>As Pete cursed the Penguin under his breath; they heard a lone howl off in the distance.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="25">
              <Text>Pete scanned the horizon and saw a wolf, howling sadly.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="26">
              <Text>“Let’s go have a look, shall we?” Bob suggested, and they both went to the wolf.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="27">
              <Text>“People… What are you doing here?” the wolf was very nervous.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="28">
              <Text>“Ye best be askin’ someone else, I don’t know what the hell is goin’ on anymore, talking animals and all,” Pete rambled.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="29">
              <Text>“Shush Pete.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="30">
              <Text>We are just passing through the area,” Bob explained.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="31">
              <Text>“Oh, okay then… move along and leave me alone please…” The wolf said.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="32">
              <Text>“Well let’s get going then,” Bob started waddling off again, and the wolf lowered his head in despair.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="33">
              <Text>“Now wait a minute,” Pete said, noticing the injustice “What be makin’ ye so sad?”</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="34">
              <Text>“Well… it’s my wife, we had an argument… and… well…” The wolf sniffled.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="35">
              <Text>Oi get th’ point.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="36">
              <Text>It be soundin’ like one o’ them arguments ‘bout nuthin’” Pete said.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="37">
              <Text>After some coaxing, Pete got the wolf to take him to where he thought his wife was, and they found her howling just as he had been.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="38">
              <Text>And they did rejoice.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="39">
              <Text>know what yer problem was, ye dinna fergive each other.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="40">
              <Text>Ye be needin’ compassion, or else where d’ye end up?</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="41">
              <Text>All alone.” Pete said.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="42">
              <Text>And Thus did Fearsome Pirate Pete learn Compassion.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="43">
              <Text>Fearsome Pirate Pete and Bob walked for even more than before they had met the wolf.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="44">
              <Text>Until, that is, until they saw some movement in the distance ahead.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="45">
              <Text>Pete and Bob picked up speed and caught up with the movement.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="46">
              <Text>Twas a snake an a gerbil, conversing about different types of cheese.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="47">
              <Text>“Oi, what’er ye doin’ here?” Pete said.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="48">
              <Text>“Us?” asked the gerbil.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="49">
              <Text>“Excuse my smelly friend’s rudeness of interrupting you. but we are curious to as how you are here” responded bob.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="50">
              <Text>“Well, I was returning home, and I ran into this snake, no doubt the same way you two met each other,” The gerbil said.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="51">
              <Text>“well, I’ma bet on not bein’ thar exact same way,” Pete said, looking at Bob’s beak.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="52">
              <Text>“At first I was afraid I would be eaten, but thankfully this snake is compassionate,” The gerbil explained.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="53">
              <Text>“Ah yes, we know much of compassion,” Bob said.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="54">
              <Text>“Yes, well, we really should be on our way;” Said the snake.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="55">
              <Text>“Not to worry, we’re both going in the same direction.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="56">
              <Text>I’m sure we would love to see your family Mr. Gerbil.”</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="57">
              <Text>“Yes! As they say, the more the merrier!”</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="58">
              <Text>For the rest of the trip to the Gerbils home, the Gerbil talked about his family.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="59">
              <Text>When they came to the Gerbils home, he called for his family to come out and meet the guests.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="60">
              <Text>“Oh, I’ll have to make many extra portions tonight” said Mrs. Gerbil.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="61">
              <Text>“No, no, we do not intended to intrude upon your home.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="62">
              <Text>Besides , I doubt we’d fit in,” Bob said, looking at Pete.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="63">
              <Text>“Of course, how silly of me. Mr. snake, will we have you for dinner?” Mrs. Gerbil asked.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="64">
              <Text>“No, it is I who shall have you for dinner!” the snake said.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="65">
              <Text>Suddenly, he lunged at Mrs. Gerbil with his mouth gaping wide open.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="66">
              <Text>Pete grabbed him by the neck.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="67">
              <Text>“Argh, a traitor have we?” Pete said.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="68">
              <Text>Mr. Gerbil was absolutely shocked.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="69">
              <Text>“I’m so sorry, I should’ve known he was fooling me,” he confessed to Pete.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="70">
              <Text>“Nar, s’not yer fault.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="71">
              <Text>Trustworthiness is important for all, and those who deceive are bound t’ be found out eventually, and dealt with justly.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="72">
              <Text>Speaking of which,” Pete grabbed the snake by the tail, and started swinging him around wildly.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="73">
              <Text>He finally let go, sending the snake off into the horizon.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="74">
              <Text>“Thank you, if you were not here, I doubt I could have defended myself,” Mr. Gerbil said.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="75">
              <Text>“Not at all.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="76">
              <Text>We are merely being good subjects of his Noodliness,” Bob replied.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="77">
              <Text>And thus did Fearsome Pirate Pete learn the importance of trustworthiness.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="78">
              <Text>As well as the importance of not eating gerbils.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="79">
              <Text>They left the Gerbils home, and set off again.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="80">
              <Text>They walked so far, they felt as if they could not go any farther, as if they had walked round the world.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="81">
              <Text>Then Pete spotted a Polar Bear in the distance, prowling and pacing, as if guarding something.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="82">
              <Text>“Ye think we should go up to it?</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="83">
              <Text>It looks like its guarding its territory,” Pete commented.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="84">
              <Text>“It’s your call Pete,” Bob responded.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="85">
              <Text>“Oi be sayin’ we wait and see if it goes away.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="86">
              <Text>Oi don’t want t’ be mauled before the fest.”</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="87">
              <Text>“Then let’s try and get some rest first.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="88">
              <Text>Who knows how long that bear will be there?” Bob suggested.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="89">
              <Text>They slept, and after waking up, Pete saw that the bear was still there, but asleep.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="90">
              <Text>He woke Bob, and they tried creeping past it.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="91">
              <Text>The bear awoke.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="92">
              <Text>“Augh!</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="93">
              <Text>Stay away!</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="94">
              <Text>Don’t hurt me again!” it yelled, jumping away from them.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="95">
              <Text>“Calm down ol’ chap, we mean you no harm.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="96">
              <Text>How are you hurt?” Bob asked in a calm voice.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="97">
              <Text>“It’s my paw.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="98">
              <Text>I was in a fight over territory and the other bear bit my paw,” The bear explained.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="99">
              <Text>“’Ere, I was saving this fer me own flesh wounds, but I think it’ll help ye.”</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="100">
              <Text>Pete said, pulling out a bandana, and wrapping it around the bear’s paw.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="101">
              <Text>“I saw you there before.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="102">
              <Text>I was hoping you’d help me,” the bear said.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="103">
              <Text>Pete did not respond.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="104">
              <Text>“Pete,” Bob said sternly. 4: 27 “Arr, we was afraid ye’d maul us.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="105">
              <Text>Ah suppose Oi was a little prejudice on ye,” Pete confessed.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="106">
              <Text>“Right, Pete, you shouldn’t judge people just because of the way they look or appear to be acting,” Bob said.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="107">
              <Text>“Thanks guys, I’m off to reclaim my territory,” the bear said as he went off into the other direction, limping a little.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="108">
              <Text>And thus did Pete learn not to be Prejudice.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="109">
              <Text>Now, not too much farther on their travels, they came across a human, apparently throwing tree trunks.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="110">
              <Text>“Oi, what’re ye doing?” Pete yelled.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="111">
              <Text>“Tha Caber Toss!” the man replied proudly.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="112">
              <Text>“Ah ahm Scott. The best tosser o’ cabers in all o’ Scotland!”</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="113">
              <Text>“But, we be in Norway,” Pete said, still confused.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="114">
              <Text>“Ach, that’s exactly why Ah ahm ‘ere.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="115">
              <Text>T’ prove to all that Ah ahm the best tosser o’ cabers in all th’ world!” he said, throwing another caber.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="116">
              <Text>It flipped once.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="117">
              <Text>“Argh!</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="118">
              <Text>Sounds like a challenge!</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="119">
              <Text>Lemme try,” Pete requested.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="120">
              <Text>He picked up a caber, and threw it.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="121">
              <Text>The caber bounced twice.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="122">
              <Text>“Ach, not too shabby,” Scott said.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="123">
              <Text>He threw another one, but still it only bounced once.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="124">
              <Text>Then Scott ran off crying like baby.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="125">
              <Text>“Yar, serves ‘im right, braggin bout being the best.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="126">
              <Text>ahm the best Oi am!</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="127">
              <Text>Oi be bettin’ I can beat anyone in this’er world,” Pete boasted.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="128">
              <Text>“You seem to have learned nothing from Scott,” Bob said as he picked up a caber, and threw it.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="129">
              <Text>The caber bounced four times.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="130">
              <Text>“Ach, suppose I should’na brag unless I know I’m right,” Pete said.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="131">
              <Text>“Actually, you should not at all.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="132">
              <Text>Remember, there is always someone out there who is better than you at whatever it is you’re doing,” Bob explained.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="133">
              <Text>“Arr, Oi’ll be rememberin that,” Pete said.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="134">
              <Text>And Thus did Pete learn Humbleness.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="135">
              <Text>Pete and Bob continued on their trek again.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="136">
              <Text>They could almost make out the smoke coming from Norse lodge when Bob yelled out in pain.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="137">
              <Text>happened?” Pete asked as he looked down at Bob’s foot.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="138">
              <Text>He had been stabbed by a pointy stick.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="139">
              <Text>Pete pulled it out.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="140">
              <Text>“Thank you, Pete,” Bob said.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="141">
              <Text>“Can ye walk?” Pete asked.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="142">
              <Text>“Yes, it’s not much farther, let’s go” Bob claimed, but he was limping like a pirate with two peg legs.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="143">
              <Text>At one point he fell down.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="144">
              <Text>“Bob, Lemme carry you,” Pete offered.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="145">
              <Text>“No, that’s alright, I can make it,” Bob protested.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="146">
              <Text>But he had great difficulty getting up and moving again.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="147">
              <Text>Pete picked him up, and carried him the rest of the way to the Norse lodge.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="148">
              <Text>He set Bob down outside the lodge.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="149">
              <Text>“Now, honestly, can ye walk?” Pete asked.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="150">
              <Text>“Yes, I will be fine from here,”</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="151">
              <Text>Bob confirmed, “Go and have fun with your friends at the festival.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="152">
              <Text>I have farther to go.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="153">
              <Text>Thank you, Pete.”</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="154">
              <Text>“Arr, If’n ye ever be in the Caribbean, just follow the trail of wrecked ships and the smell of pasta.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="155">
              <Text>You’ll find me,” Pete said.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="156">
              <Text>“I will be sure to,” Bob said.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="157">
              <Text>With that, he waddled off into the distance.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="158">
              <Text>Thus did Pete learn Loyalty.</Text>
            </Verse>
          </Verses>
        </Chapter>
        <Chapter Number="3">
          <Verses>
            <Verse Number="1">
              <Text>Upon entering the Norse Lodge, Pete beheld a most distressing scene.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="2">
              <Text>The feast table seated many hairy and well armored Norsemen, as well as many pirates of his crew.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="3">
              <Text>At the head of the table, however, was a relatively small, clean cut and shaven man in humble, sober black robes.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="4">
              <Text>The distressing part was the portions of the food, as well as the food itself.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="5">
              <Text>It was mostly pork rinds and other low-carb options, and in small portions, too.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="6">
              <Text>Tiny and Ushnor were seated near the entrance, so Pete went to sit by them.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="7">
              <Text>“Whart in the good name o’ Pasta be this kind o’feast?” Pete asked.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="8">
              <Text>“It seems that in my absence, this Olaf character has come and forced everyone into Aktinsceticism,” Ushnor explained, indicating the man in black.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="9">
              <Text>“Some idea of a feast, eh?” Tiny added.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="10">
              <Text>Suddenly, one of the feasting Vikings shoved his plate back, and stood up.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="11">
              <Text>“I refuse to eat this crap!</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="12">
              <Text>Give me some good swill, instead!” he shouted.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="13">
              <Text>Olaf closed his eyes, slowly got up, and moved around the table to the Viking in question.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="14">
              <Text>As he went, he passed a fireplace.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="15">
              <Text>Olaf picked up a long, sharp piece of metal, and stuck it in the fire for a few moments.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="16">
              <Text>Once he seemed satisfied, he pulled it out and continued over to the Viking.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="17">
              <Text>The Viking stood his ground, and faced Olaf.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="18">
              <Text>He towered over him, yet did not raise a hand against him.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="19">
              <Text>Olaf raised his implement, and stabbed the Viking in the eye, twisting and pressing the hot metal against it.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="20">
              <Text>The Viking resisted as much as he could, though he still had to let out yells of pain.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="21">
              <Text>really don’t know what’s best for you,” Olaf told him coldly, “You really should listen to what I have to say.”</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="22">
              <Text>enough of this crap,” Ushnor said, slamming his fist down.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="23">
              <Text>He picked up his hammer and ran across the table to Olaf, building as much momentum for his strike.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="24">
              <Text>Olaf was able to avoid getting hit, and brandished his poker as a weapon.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="25">
              <Text>“Don’t toy with me, boy, I’ve got science on my side!” Olaf boasted.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="26">
              <Text>The other Vikings saw this, and realizes they could resist, so they took their weapons in hand, and surrounded Olaf.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="27">
              <Text>“Why didn’t we just do this earlier?” One asked Another.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="28">
              <Text>“Narrator wasn’t here.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="29">
              <Text>That pirate guy who just arrive must be the main character or something,” replied Another.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="30">
              <Text>“You always have the best explanations, Another,” One complimented Another.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="31">
              <Text>“You are too kind, One,” Another said.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="32">
              <Text>“Let’s burn his eyes out, see how he likes that!” One said.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="33">
              <Text>The others yelled in agreement.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="34">
              <Text>“Friends, we cannot do that!” Ushnor cried, trying to contain their anger.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="35">
              <Text>“If someone uses an immoral or low tactic against us, we can’t just go right around and do the same thing to them.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="36">
              <Text>If we think it’s an outrageous thing to do, we should not do it ourselves,” Ushnor continued.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="37">
              <Text>“Well, how about we ask the injured party?” Another suggested.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="38">
              <Text>They all turned to the Viking who now had one blind eye.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="39">
              <Text>“An eye for an eye leaves the whole world blind.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="40">
              <Text>Besides, eyepatches are badass,” he responded.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="41">
              <Text>“I couldn’t have said it better myself,” Ushnor said.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="42">
              <Text>“Yarr,” Pete chimed in, “Ye make th’ Flying Spaghetti Monster proud, ye do.”</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="43">
              <Text>The Vikings threw Olaf out into the cold, and vowed to leave him untouched, provided he stay away from the frozen northlands forever more.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="44">
              <Text>Pete spent the next week helping them prepare for a proper feast.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="45">
              <Text>Without being overbearing, he explained to them his religion of Pastafarianism, and made quite a few converts.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="46">
              <Text>At his suggestion, the feast included large portions of Pasta, and they all ate heartily, receiving the love of the Flying Spaghetti Monster, even those who did not convert.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="47">
              <Text>After the festivities, it was time for Pete to return to the Caribbean.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="48">
              <Text>Having now ship, and a significantly reduced crew, the Vikings made a sturdy vessel for him, and many signed on as his crew.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="49">
              <Text>Finally, with a full crew and a quality ship, Pete and his crew set sail for the Caribbean.</Text>
            </Verse>
          </Verses>
        </Chapter>
        <Chapter Number="4">
          <Verses>
            <Verse Number="1">
              <Text>For two and forty nights and two and forty days, they did sail, until all the slush was gone, and the waters were warm, and full of fish.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="2">
              <Text>The air was crisp, and the winds full of promise.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="3">
              <Text>But the pirates were concerned when they made port.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="4">
              <Text>There seemed to be no people in the streets, no drunkards boozing about, being slapped by wenches, no taverns overflowing with brawls, and generally not a lot of pirating going on.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="5">
              <Text>There were boats at the docks, and nothing seemed destroyed.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="6">
              <Text>In fact, everything seemed to be in a much better state than when they left.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="7">
              <Text>“Yarr, Oi don’t be liken this one bit,” Pete growled.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="8">
              <Text>“Oi’ll check around town.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="9">
              <Text>You lot stay here.”</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="10">
              <Text>“You sure it’s a good idea to go alone, eh?” Tiny asked.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="11">
              <Text>“Yarr, good point.” Pete said.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="12">
              <Text>“You come with me, Tiny. Ushnor, stay an’ guard the ship,” He commanded.”</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="13">
              <Text>Pete and Tiny explored the seemingly desolate town.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="14">
              <Text>There were some signs of life, as they were continually watched by people from alley ways and from inside buildings.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="15">
              <Text>They were not sinister, but they looked as if they knew what was going on, and they pitied Pete.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="16">
              <Text>Suddenly, Pete and Tiny were apprehended from behind by ninjas.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="17">
              <Text>“Whart in th’ name o’ Tortellini?” Pete exclaimed.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="18">
              <Text>“Our master would like a word with you” One of the ninjas whispered in his ear.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="19">
              <Text>The ninjas took Pete and Tiny to an underground lair beneath an Italian restaurant.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="20">
              <Text>They tied them to chairs in a small dark room, across from a table.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="21">
              <Text>Nikta sat at the table, eating a reasonable portion of Pasta.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="22">
              <Text>“Would you like some pasta, Petey?</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="23">
              <Text>It’s Capellini,” Nikta offered.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="24">
              <Text>Pete spat.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="25">
              <Text>“Oi wouldn’t accept anything from ye, ye diseased maniac,” Pete said.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="26">
              <Text>“Whart’ve ye done t’ this place anyhow, and why?”</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="27">
              <Text>“Oh, just a little good natured dictatorship.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="28">
              <Text>The people need to be told what to do and think,” Nikta explained.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="29">
              <Text>I hear you ran into my friend Olaf in the northlands, is that true?”</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="30">
              <Text>“Yarr, we ran him out but good.” Pete bragged.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="31">
              <Text>“But how did ye return?</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="32">
              <Text>Oi thought th’ Flying Spaghetti Monster had taken good care o’ ye back in the first chapter.”</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="33">
              <Text>“Not really, he merely apprehended me, and then you all forgot about me and went into a description of creation,” Nikta explained.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="34">
              <Text>“Quite rude, really.”</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="35">
              <Text>“Oi’ll remember me manners next time someone assaults me with a hoard of ninjas,” Pete retorted.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="36">
              <Text>“Whart exactly is it that ye want from me, matey?”</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="37">
              <Text>“Why, nothing more than your ultimate demise,” Nikta said simply.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="38">
              <Text>“Tiny, would you like to do the honors?”</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="39">
              <Text>“What, you want me, eh?” Tiny asked.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="40">
              <Text>“Oh yes, I think it will be a delicious ending to Pete’s life.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="41">
              <Text>You do this for me, and I’ll grant you with a position of wealth, influence, and favor,” Nikta offered. Tiny smiled a sinister smile in response. Nikta motioned to his guards, and Tiny was cut loose.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="42">
              <Text>Tiny was given a katana, and stabbed Pete through the chest.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="43">
              <Text>Instantly, Tiny grew three feet, for the love of the Flying Spaghetti Monster had left him.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="44">
              <Text>Pete found himself in a beautiful, white space.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="45">
              <Text>As his senses adjusted to his location, he did notice the Flying Spaghetti Monster.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="46">
              <Text>“Whart happened to Nikta?</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="47">
              <Text>And Tiny, th’ mutinious bastard!</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="48">
              <Text>And whart about Ushnor and me crew?” Pete asked, growing more concerned as he remembered more of his recent adventures.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="49">
              <Text>“Worry not, smelly friend,” The Flying Spaghetti Monster assured him.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="50">
              <Text>“Tiny has gotten his just desserts, and I informed Ushnor of what Nikta had done; he’ll be taking care of those ninjas shortly.”</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="51">
              <Text>“Arrgh, that’s good.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="52">
              <Text>So I’m dead, and this is heaven?” Pete asked, just to be sure.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="53">
              <Text>“Yes, Pete.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="54">
              <Text>You have done well.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="55">
              <Text>You have shown strength in the face of adversity, and much perseverance.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="56">
              <Text>I award you with the finest grog and best stripping wenches in the cosmos.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="57">
              <Text>Is there anything else you wish for?” The Great Noodly One did ask.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="58">
              <Text>“Oi spent me life on th’ seas, now I see heaven has no Caribbean, or Pacific ocean, or even a Lake Michigan of any sort,” Pete mused.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="59">
              <Text>“Not t’ be takin’ this personally, yer Pastaliness, but Oi find it rather atrocious to not have a large body of water fer piratin’.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="60">
              <Text>If I could have one wish, it would be for there to be a great, endless Caribbean with islands ripe for the pillaging, and tohers with beautiful scenery and nifty hiding places.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="61">
              <Text>That no matter how far ye travel, there always be somethin’ ye can explore or pillage, and that there never be an end to th’ adventure.”</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="62">
              <Text>“So be it,” The Flying Spaghetti Monster declared.</Text>
            </Verse>
            <Verse Number="63">
              <Text>“Let it be known from this day forth, there shall be an Endless Caribbean, and any who wish may join or create a pirate crew to pillage and explore the vastness of Heaven’s Caribbean.”</Text>
            </Verse>
          </Verses>
        </Chapter>
      </Chapters>
      <Abbreviation>fpp</Abbreviation>
    </Book>
    <Book Number="11">
      <FileName>page14.htm</FileName>
      <Name>Empty</Name>
      <Chapters />
      <Abbreviation>11</Abbreviation>
    </Book>
    <Book Number="12">
      <FileName>page15.htm</FileName>
      <Name>Empty</Name>
      <Chapters />
      <Abbreviation>12</Abbreviation>
    </Book>
    <Book Number="13">
      <FileName>page16.htm</FileName>
      <Name>Empty</Name>
      <Chapters />
      <Abbreviation>13</Abbreviation>
    </Book>
    <Book Number="14">
      <FileName>page17.htm</FileName>
      <Name>Empty</Name>
      <Chapters />
      <Abbreviation>14</Abbreviation>
    </Book>
    <Book Number="15">
      <FileName>page18.htm</FileName>
      <Name>Empty</Name>
      <Chapters />
      <Abbreviation>15</Abbreviation>
    </Book>
    <Book Number="16">
      <FileName>page19.htm</FileName>
      <Name>Empty</Name>
      <Chapters />
      <Abbreviation>16</Abbreviation>
    </Book>
    <Book Number="17">
      <FileName>page20.htm</FileName>
      <Name>Empty</Name>
      <Chapters />
      <Abbreviation>17</Abbreviation>
    </Book>
    <Book Number="18">
      <FileName>page21.htm</FileName>
      <Name>Empty</Name>
      <Chapters />
      <Abbreviation>18</Abbreviation>
    </Book>
    <Book Number="19">
      <FileName>page22.htm</FileName>
      <Name>Empty</Name>
      <Chapters />
      <Abbreviation>19</Abbreviation>
    </Book>
    <Book Number="20">
      <FileName>page23.htm</FileName>
      <Name>Empty</Name>
      <Chapters />
      <Abbreviation>20</Abbreviation>
    </Book>
    <Book Number="21">
      <FileName>page24.htm</FileName>
      <Name>Empty</Name>
      <Chapters />
      <Abbreviation>21</Abbreviation>
    </Book>
    <Book Number="22">
      <FileName>page25.htm</FileName>
      <Name>Empty</Name>
      <Chapters />
      <Abbreviation>22</Abbreviation>
    </Book>
    <Book Number="23">
      <FileName>page26.htm</FileName>
      <Name>Empty</Name>
      <Chapters />
      <Abbreviation>23</Abbreviation>
    </Book>
    <Book Number="24">
      <FileName>page27.htm</FileName>
      <Name>Empty</Name>
      <Chapters />
      <Abbreviation>24</Abbreviation>
    </Book>
    <Book Number="25">
      <FileName>page28.htm</FileName>
      <Name>Empty</Name>
      <Chapters />
      <Abbreviation>25</Abbreviation>
    </Book>
    <Book Number="26">
      <FileName>page29.htm</FileName>
      <Name>Empty</Name>
      <Chapters />
      <Abbreviation>26</Abbreviation>
    </Book>
    <Book Number="27">
      <FileName>page30.htm</FileName>
      <Name>Empty</Name>
      <Chapters />
      <Abbreviation>27</Abbreviation>
    </Book>
    <Book Number="28">
      <FileName>page31.htm</FileName>
      <Name>Empty</Name>
      <Chapters />
      <Abbreviation>28</Abbreviation>
    </Book>
    <Book Number="29">
      <FileName>page32.htm</FileName>
      <Name>Empty</Name>
      <Chapters />
      <Abbreviation>29</Abbreviation>
    </Book>
    <Book Number="30">
      <FileName>page33.htm</FileName>
      <Name>Empty</Name>
      <Chapters />
      <Abbreviation>30</Abbreviation>
    </Book>
    <Book Number="31">
      <FileName>page34.htm</FileName>
      <Name>Empty</Name>
      <Chapters />
      <Abbreviation>31</Abbreviation>
    </Book>
    <Book Number="32">
      <FileName>page35.htm</FileName>
      <Name>Empty</Name>
      <Chapters />
      <Abbreviation>32</Abbreviation>
    </Book>
    <Book Number="33">
      <FileName>page36.htm</FileName>
      <Name>Empty</Name>
      <Chapters />
      <Abbreviation>33</Abbreviation>
    </Book>
    <Book Number="34">
      <FileName>page37.htm</FileName>
      <Name>Empty</Name>
      <Chapters />
      <Abbreviation>34</Abbreviation>
    </Book>
    <Book Number="35">
      <FileName>page38.htm</FileName>
      <Name>Empty</Name>
      <Chapters />
      <Abbreviation>35</Abbreviation>
    </Book>
    <Book Number="36">
      <FileName>page39.htm</FileName>
      <Name>Empty</Name>
      <Chapters />
      <Abbreviation>36</Abbreviation>
    </Book>
    <Book Number="37">
      <FileName>page40.htm</FileName>
      <Name>Empty</Name>
      <Chapters />
      <Abbreviation>37</Abbreviation>
    </Book>
    <Book Number="38">
      <FileName>page41.htm</FileName>
      <Name>Empty</Name>
      <Chapters />
      <Abbreviation>38</Abbreviation>
    </Book>
    <Book Number="39">
      <FileName>page42.htm</FileName>
      <Name>Empty</Name>
      <Chapters />
      <Abbreviation>39</Abbreviation>
    </Book>
    <Book Number="40">
      <FileName>page43.htm</FileName>
      <Name>Empty</Name>
      <Chapters />
      <Abbreviation>40</Abbreviation>
    </Book>
    <Book Number="41">
      <FileName>page44.htm</FileName>
      <Name>Empty</Name>
      <Chapters />
      <Abbreviation>41</Abbreviation>
    </Book>
    <Book Number="42">
      <FileName>page45.htm</FileName>
      <Name>Empty</Name>
      <Chapters />
      <Abbreviation>42</Abbreviation>
    </Book>
    <Book Number="43">
      <FileName>page46.htm</FileName>
      <Name>Empty</Name>
      <Chapters />
      <Abbreviation>43</Abbreviation>
    </Book>
    <Book Number="44">
      <FileName>page47.htm</FileName>
      <Name>Empty</Name>
      <Chapters />
      <Abbreviation>44</Abbreviation>
    </Book>
    <Book Number="45">
      <FileName>page48.htm</FileName>
      <Name>Empty</Name>
      <Chapters />
      <Abbreviation>45</Abbreviation>
    </Book>
    <Book Number="46">
      <FileName>page49.htm</FileName>
      <Name>Empty</Name>
      <Chapters />
      <Abbreviation>46</Abbreviation>
    </Book>
    <Book Number="47">
      <FileName>page50.htm</FileName>
      <Name>Empty</Name>
      <Chapters />
      <Abbreviation>47</Abbreviation>
    </Book>
    <Book Number="48">
      <FileName>page51.htm</FileName>
      <Name>Empty</Name>
      <Chapters />
      <Abbreviation>48</Abbreviation>
    </Book>
    <Book Number="49">
      <FileName>page52.htm</FileName>
      <Name>Empty</Name>
      <Chapters />
      <Abbreviation>49</Abbreviation>
    </Book>
    <Book Number="50">
      <FileName>page53.htm</FileName>
      <Name>Empty</Name>
      <Chapters />
      <Abbreviation>50</Abbreviation>
    </Book>
    <Book Number="51">
      <FileName>page54.htm</FileName>
      <Name>Empty</Name>
      <Chapters />
      <Abbreviation>51</Abbreviation>
    </Book>
    <Book Number="52">
      <FileName>page55.htm</FileName>
      <Name>Empty</Name>
      <Chapters />
      <Abbreviation>52</Abbreviation>
    </Book>
  </Books>
</LooseCanon>